Good day everyone.  [music] Now
we will review Whoife L by Sunl
Philippines, Sunfet and Well
Advantage.  This provides a lump sum
amount when we are diagnosed
with a critical illness or chronic disease or
when we pass away.  [music]
This is a financial solution that
we really need to have because
[music] chronic illnesses often
drain the money we've saved for
years.  How much does [music] cost to
get sick?  Here we will see the top
five that cause deadly diseases [music] and
deadly expenses in the pocket.  Here's
the estimated cost of how much
we often spend when
we have these types of [music]
illnesses such as heart disease, cancer,
stroke, diabetes and COVID-19.  [music]
And did you know that last 2021,
COVID was in the top three most deadliest illnesses
but as reported by DOH [music] right now it's
only in the top 11.  The sunfit and
well advantage [music] has
critical illness insurance, hospital
income benefits related to
his critical illness [music] when
you are hospitalized.  It also has
life insurance or debt benefits.
This [music] also has cash benefits or
savings.  And the main purpose of
this product is for health and [music] life.
So if you are looking for a plan that
has an investment component, this is not what
you are looking for.  This
[music] is also not like an HMO or health card that we
can use if we want to get a
checkup.  getting a lab test or [music]
so when you're hospitalized it's an
emergency.  Critical health insurance
is reimbursement [music]
when claiming it and cash benefits are
provided.  It is a gift
that [music] can be used to pay for
expenses incurred in operations, surgeries, or
serious illnesses.  [music] When it comes to the
coverage year of HMO, it is often only until age
65 years old and often until
age 100 years old for health
insurance.  [music]
As for the HMO, you have to
use it with accredited doctors and
hospitals.  Whereas with health
insurance, you have the [music] choice of
which hospital and
which doctor you choose.  If
you ask me [music], what is
more important to Miss Jona to take?   It is
important that both have this
type of health plan protection because
their uses are different
.  This is the health insurance
plan of Sunfit and Well.  [music]
It also has a savings component.  First,
he has what are called dividends.
It's given away or it usually comes out
after paying [music] years for
its release.  Usually on the second
year, he has it immediately, but
it is only released after the
paying years.  Like [music] for example
on the 11th year if you took out 10 years to pay
or in the [music] LS 16th
year when you took out 15 years to pay
or on the 21st year [music]
if you took out 20 years to pay
like in this example.  Usually
around 3.9% [music] 9% is
given by Sunlife as
[music]
you kill me
and
giving [music] me wind
some kind of butterfly [music]
baby you me
[music]
up my
don't me
oh
i don't [music] win it b
and
[music]
Don't over it baby
just [music]
baby you me [music]
you giving me wind
some kind [music] of butterfly
You me [music]
you my [music]
don't me
[music]
but I don't j it baby
not [music] get
but I don't miss you [music]
so
by
[music]
May you me
butterfly
[music]
baby you me
my [music]
don't me
[music] you
[music]
B you
don't me [music]
Oh oh oh Oh oh
[music]
oh
โ [music]
[music] [
music]
that proves that you are
really totally disabled to wave the
premium of our policy.  [music]
Here we go.  Let's take a look at the benefits
of this plan.  Let's prioritize health
insurance benefit number one, which is
prevention.  [music]
You can avail of this special access and
privileges to premium workouts and
various wellness activities that will
help you stay [music] fit and healthy.
Just check out Go Well to explore
the wellness community.
Next is the diagnosis.  This is the
main [musical] highlight.  The first thing
we will talk about is the major critical
illness.  There are 64 illnesses
on the list [music], so you can claim
100% of the original face amount
[music], which is, for example,
1 million less the minor critical
illness claim if any.  [music] For
the 34 minor critical illnesses
covered by this, the maximum benefit that
can be claimed here is 50% of the
original phase amount.  For the first claim
[music] and second claims, it is 20% and the
third claim is 10%.  So
[music] means that one can claim up to three times
when it comes to
minors.  However, [music]
our claims are that this should be from a different
group of minor critical illnesses.  So
for example, the [music] first
diagnosis of minor critical illness is
in the heart-related group.
The
following [music] minor illnesses must be in a different category or group for a
claim to be made.  There are groupings of
illnesses here, so if your illness
falls into one of the 16 specific cancer
conditions, there is an additional 50%
[music]
on top of the original phase amount
.  When cancer strikes, the
medical expenses are obviously
very expensive.  No joke.  Because of this
he has an additional 50%.  If
the pace amount is 1 million, [music] you still have an
additional Php500,000
on top of your major CB claim.  To
Summit, [music] the total illnesses
covered by the Sun and Fit and Well
advantage are at 114. Did
you know that this is the highest
covered [music] illness in the market?
Because most of the time,
you'll only see additional critical illness in
their VUL plans [music], like 36 only.  So
if the illness you suffer from is not
on this list, it doesn't matter what
critical [music] illness benefit
you paid for.  Without a doubt, this is
considered the best [music] health
insurance in the market.  Just take note
that the policy terminates
upon death [music] of the insured
or upon claims that all total 100%
of the original phase amount.  Let's go
to treatment and rehabilitation.  The
number [music] three and four.
Claiming this is once for
minor and once for major.
Remember, [music] the CB in minor is up
to three claims can be done with
different group of illness.  [music]
When it comes to treatment and
rehabilitation, once we have claimed
it for the first minor critical
illness benefit, the
next time you have a minor
critical illness benefit,
the treatment [music] and
rehabilitation will no longer be available.  But if you ever have
a major CB again, this
treatment and rehabilitation [music] will be additional
to what will be provided.  So how does it work?
Let's go to the treatment that [music]
he has hospital income and post
hospitalization benefits.  The hospital
income benefit [musika] has
0.125%
of the original phase amount [musika]
per day with a maximum of 90 days
confinement or 3 months when claiming.
Example [music]
1 million phase amount
1225% which is 1,250 [music]
per day the client's daily hospital income
benefit.  [music] So if
he is ever hospitalized for 90 days,
he can still claim an additional 112,500
[music]
on top of the critical illness claim.
He still has an additional fixed
[music] amount of Php5,000 for the post
hospitalization benefit.
This is also on top of his critical illness claim
.  Of course, we need to recover
so we can leave the hospital and we
also need money for expenses.
[music]
Because of this, he will also receive a
home recovery benefit that is an additional 50%
of the hospital income [music] benefit.
So, our example earlier was that
he was confined for 90 days with a total of 112,500.
What he [music] can claim this time
is that he still has an additional 50%
which is Php56,250.  [music]
Mrs. can also claim 10% of the face amount or Php100,000.  Dela Cruz is a
bread winner if he becomes terminally ill
with a life expectancy [music] of 6
months or below.  This is the type
whose life has a limit.  Since
[music] we have a specific cancer
booster benefit that provides an
additional 50% [music] of the original
phe amount, it also includes this treatment and
rehabilitation [music] part
.  After the
client is discharged from the hospital [musika] if
qualified for the specific cancer
booster, there is an additional 50%
[musika] from the total amounting to the
daily hospital income benefit, post
hospitalization, home recovery, and
[musika] palliative care benefit if
any.  The insured here must
still be alive [music] when he is discharged
from the hospital to be eligible
to claim [music]
this kind of cancer booster for
treatment and rehabilitation part.
[music]
Now, let's break down all the
benefits.  Let's say we have sample
scenario number one.  Mrs.  Dela Cruz,
for example, was diagnosed with invasive
[music] cancer under that of major
critical illness.  So it doesn't matter that he claimed 100% of the face
amount which is Php1
million.  If his disease falls into the specific cancer
category, [music]
there is an additional cancer booster
benefit of Php500,000.
That's the 50% original PACE amount.
[music]
less the minor claim if they have any
deductions.  If he was hospitalized
for 90 days and discharged alive,
he would have an additional Php112,500
[music]
for HIV.  Home recovery is Php56,250
and post hospitalization is Php5,000.
And since he was diagnosed with specific cancer,
[music] has an additional 50%
additional benefits from the treatment
and rehabilitation.  [music]
This is the total he can claim
in this scenario [music] around
1,760,715 and
then [music]
his policy will be terminated.  If
the client disappears, there will be no debt
benefit or insurance claim to be obtained
because everything has already been taken.  Let's go
to sample [music] number two.  Scenario.
For example, Mrs.  Dela Cruz needs
surgical removal of one kidney
[music]
which is under the minor illness kidney related
group.  He can claim 20% of the
original phase amount of Pillon which is
Php200,000.  [music]
And if he is hospitalized, let's say for
60 days, this can still be obtained.
His total claims for this
scenario are around Php317,500.
[music]
The most common question is this.
What benefits are left if you have already claimed
for the first minor illness?  Can
he claim
20% of the original phase amount for the second [music] and 10%
if there is a third claim?
[music] Which is total of minor claims
is 50%.  Then the next claims must be in a different group
of illnesses again
.  [music]
And the remaining benefit can be
used for his major critical
illness or when called by St.  Peter
because it's still 100 [music] years old
.
If we notice, there are so many
added benefits on [music]
on top of the critical illness benefit that
we can use for treatment and
recovery.  The 1 million
[music] face amount we made earlier is
just a sample and can be
adjusted depending on the budget desired or
how much coverage is
required.  [music]
But then again, don't forget that
we still have cash savings just in case
we don't use it.  This is
only a limited pay and we have the option to
pay.  [music] if 10 years, 15 years, or
20 years.  In our example, Mrs.
Dela Cruz, a nonsmoker [musician]
and 30 years old who wants 1 million
coverage, this is the option
he chooses.  [music] We can see here that
we can get it cheaper if
the mode of payment is annual because that's discounted.
Compared to quarterly payments,
[music] has interest on
his payment.  The interest rate is 10% when paid
quarterly and 6% when paid semi-annually.
We can also notice that
the 20 years to pay is less [music] because the
payment number of years has been shortened.  And now
I'll show you the best
move we can apply to the [music]
Sunfit and Well advantage.  At the age of
30 years old, if you take it, it's
only 300,000 coverage in [music].  The
quarterly fee is only Php2,800 or
Php3,000 [music]
and the annual fee is
only Php10,000.  And if you're going to cover [music]
, the
quarter line is only around 8,000.  Now, just find out
how much [music]
your ideal budget is for your health insurance.
For more inquiries and clarification on
this plan, you may conduct your
favorite Sunlife Financial Advisor
[music]
or if you haven't already, you can also
message me on my Facebook page or
on my personal Facebook account.  See
you.